AUSTIN SHEAGLEY

STUDENT AT UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO

CONTACT

+1 951 296 7482

asheagle@ucsd.edu

• La Jolla 92037

Linkedin.com/in/ashe agley/

EDUCATION

Irvine Valley College

Cognitive Science major. Fulfilled transfer certification (IGETC) 2015-2017 3.60 GPA

University of California, San Diego

Majoring in Cognitive Science with a specialization in Design and Interaction 2017 -3.76 GPA

SKILLS

// PROFESSIONAL

- Research
- Report Writing
- Leadership
- Self-reliant

PROFILE

My highest priority is to succeed at university as I move towards my goal of achieving a B.S. in Cognitive Science with a specialization in Design and Interaction. Along this path I would also like to gain experience in Cognitive Science related fields through lab research, internships, and programs. I am open, interested, and appreciative of all fields and the knowledge and insight they provide, but my strongest interest lies in gaining more understanding in Computer Science, Engineering, Graphic Design, and Marketing.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Italki

Tutor | 2012 - 2014

Tutored pupils in beginner, intermediate, and advanced English including grammar, syntax, and colloquial usage. Lessons were conducted through text, E-mail, and Skype.

Pacific Coast Marketing

Secretary/Personal Assistant | 2014 - 2017

- Took phone calls including orders, complaints, and customer service.
- Ran personal and company errands.
- Managed office.
- Answered queries.

FASTech

Blockchain Intern | January 2018 - July 2018

- Worked on the development of an ETH based token.
- Started and maintained cloud mining via AWS.

SKILLS

// TECHNICAL

- Microsoft Office
- Python
- Java
- Solidity
- Illustrator & Photoshop

AWARDS & CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate of Completion - Blockchain for Business. Hyperledger at Linux.

Awarded for the completion of the Linux foundation's Blockchain for Business course.

IVC/SC Excellence in Research

Awarded for my group's presentation "Single-Channel N170 Collection: Developing Efficient, Affordable Neuroimaging Methods."

Provost's Honors. Fall Quarter 2017, UCSD. Awarded for GPA above 3.5.

VOLUNTEERING

Psl Beta

Volunteer and Member | 2015 - 2017

- Volunteered with the elderly and mentally handicapped.
- Conducted student research.
- Gave both oral and poster research presentations.
- Research presentations were accepted at IVC/SC at Saddleback, HTCC at UCI, SURA at Stanford, by the Western Psychological Association.

Casa Familiar

Volunteer | July 2018 - August 2018

- Worked with youth ranging from 6-13 years old.
- Tutored English.
- Conducted and monitored group activities.
- Lead team building exercises.

Yalla

Volunteer | July 2018 - Ongoing

- Worked with youth ranging 6-16 years old.
- Conducted Soccer training/exercises
- Mentored pupils in mindfulness coaching in order to improve performance and mindset.